<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Max Prettyjohns</title>
    <link>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Max Prettyjohns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Typescript Grpc Service</title>
      <link>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/typescript-grpc-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/typescript-grpc-service/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I thought I would play with typescript and GRPC a little. It seems docs on getting this up and running is a bit thin on the ground, so that makes it perfect candidate for a little blog post.
You can find example code here
To get started we need to create project, do so with the following commands
1 2 3 4  mkdir grpc-project yarn init mkdir -p src/proto yarn add typescript ts-node grpc grpc-tools ts-protoc-gen @grpc/proto-loader   now we will want to create a protoc service so we can do some tasty code generation, here is an example proto file to get started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Hugo with Travis CI</title>
      <link>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/hugo-deploy-travis-releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 01:56:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/hugo-deploy-travis-releases/</guid>
      <description>This blog is built with Hugo, and I wanted a simple way to build and then deploy it with Ansible. To do this I used Travis CI, this is relatively simple, but isn&amp;rsquo;t documented very well. So Here I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how I did it.
First up, you want a Hugo site, get started here. One simple thing that may immediately break in Travis is themes as submodules. Travis can&amp;rsquo;t deal with ssh submodules, so check your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino Volume Meter</title>
      <link>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/vmu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:22:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ma.xprettyjohns.com/posts/vmu/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently upgraded to a Audio Technica AT2020 so I can use better headphones on my home computer. Having a freestanding microphone does have its difficulties though. Keeping track of how loud I am coming through to friends is hard when I can move away from the microphone. To solve this I built an Arduino volume meter. Here I&amp;rsquo;ll go over how it works.
I wanted an excuse to write some rust and the availablity of the winapi crate seemed like a good opportunity to give it go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
